Walid Bouloukt

Full Stack Developer

I am a self-taught full stack developer, with a keen passion for building customized web solutions with streamlined functionalities and enhanced user experience. With constant learning, I keep my knowledge up to date around the latest web technologies.

Contact Info

+212 6 95 65 90 79

boulouktwalid@gmail.com

https://github.com/Walid-pro

https://walid-pro.github.io

Skills

Front End Development

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax, React, Next.js

Back End Development

Node.js, Express.js, Git, Command line

Databases

MongoDB, Mongoose

WordPress

Problem solving

Debugging

Education

China University of Geosciences 2016 - 2019

Master's degree in Public Administration

Mohammed V University 2011 - 2014

Bachelor's degree in Insurance Techniques

Certifications

Software Engineering | ALX Africa Ongoing

The Complete Web Development Bootcamp | 2021

The App Brewery, Udemy

Graphic Production | OFPPT 2011

Work Experience

- Full stack web developer Freelance August 2020 - Today
 - Tailored fully responsive and dynamic user interfaces using Next.js, React, Material UI, Bootstrap and CSS.
 - Implemented MVC architecture for web applications using Express.js.
 - Created secure Rest Apis with Node.js and Express.js.
 - Integrated payment gateways like Paypal for ecommerce store.
 - Utilized WordPress and Elementor to design high converting landing pages for Facebook Ads and Google Ads campaigns.
- SEO Assistant RemotelyWuhan Raymond Technology Co., LtdJanuary 2020 July 2020
- Webmaster and SEO Assistant Full time Wuhan Raymond Technology Co., Ltd Mars 2018 - Mai 2019
 - Develop, update and maintain company's website on Wordpress.
 - Generate high traffic keywords on "Google Ads Keyword Planner", and write articles and buying guides on Wordpress blog.

